- 어서 와
- 나 어때?
-Hey.
-Hey. So, what do you think?
머리 잘랐어? 목걸이? 옷?
New haircut? Necklace? Dress?
부츠? 부츠!
Boots? Boots!
보통 부츠보다 약간 더 비싸
실은 방값보다 비싸...
Now, they're a little more than I usually
spend on boots. Or rent.
방금 "부츠" 샀다고 한 거야
"보트" 샀다고 한 거야?
Did you say you bought "boots"
or "boats"?
알아
I know.
- 이제부터 우리 굶어야겠다
- 미안, 너무 예뻐서 그랬어
-I'll miss being able to afford food.
-I'm sorry. They just looked so good.
또 점원 표정이 "당신한텐"
The saleswoman was like:
- "너무 비싸지" 하더라구
- 맞는 말이네
-"These are too expensive for you."
-She had a point.
- 안녕
- 이럴 수가
-Hey.
-Hi. Oh, my God.
- 모니카, 부츠 너무 예쁘다
- 내 꺼야!
-Oh, Monica, those boots are amazing.
-They're mine!
- 근데 돌려줄 거야
- 돌려줘? 부츠가 듣고 있어
-Too bad we're gonna have to return them.
-Return them? They're gonna hear you.
환불 못해, 비싸지만
계속 신을 거니까 괜찮아
I'm not returning them. I know they
cost a lot, but I'll wear them all the time.
진짜야, 그리고
찬사 받는 것도 좋구
You'll see. Besides,
I love the compliments.
너무 예뻐서 누구나 원하는 걸
가진 적이 있어?
Have you ever had something
so beautiful, everyone wants it?
- 자기
- 그래도 부츠 안 돌려줄 거야
-I have you.
-Nice try. I'm keeping the boots.
프렌즈 시즌 8
'모니카의 부츠'
그래, 사랑해
That's right. I love you.
내가 항상 놀아줄게
And I'm gonna play with you
all the time.
네 사타구니에 대고
계속 말하는데 괜찮아?
How can you let him talk
to your crotch like that?
- 아기한테 말하는 거야
- 오! 그렇구나
-He's talking to the baby.
-Oh! Okay.
로스가 "네 첫 소리가 듣고
싶다"고 하길래
Okay, because when he said,
"l can't wait for your first words"..
'대단한 재주다'라고 생각했지
I thought, "There's a trick."
난 가봐야겠다
나중에 보자
Well, I gotta go, you guys.
I'll see you later.
- 안녕
- 응
-Okay. Bye.
-Bye.
내 여동생이
너한테 부탁이 있대
Hey, listen. Can you do me a favor? My
sister knows you work at Ralph Lauren..
싫어, 이제 랄프 로렌 옷
감옥에 안보낼거야
Forget it. No way. I am not sending
more Ralph Lauren clothes to prison.
- 그건 낭비야
- 아니, 그 동생 말구
-It is a waste.
-No, not her.
우리 막내 디나가 패션에
관심이 있거든
My youngest sister, Dina,
is interested in fashion.
그래서 성공한 사람의
이야기를 듣고 싶어해
She wants to talk to someone successful
to give her some advice.
- 내 상사들한테 물어볼게
- 아냐, 너랑 이야기하고 싶대
-I guess I could talk to my supervisors.
-No, she wants to talk to you.
정말? 와, 내가 이미 성공했구나
Really? Oh, my God. I'm successful.
- 그럼 만나줄 거야?
- 당연하지, 회사로 오라고 해
-Okay, so would you meet with her?
-Yes, I'd love to. Have her come by.
고마워, 만나면 너도 좋아할 거야
우리 중에 제일 영리하거든
Great, thanks. You'll love her. She's the
smartest of all the Tribbiani children.
- SAT라는 거 알아?
- 응
-Yeah, you know the SATs?
-Yeah.
그 시험도 본 애야
She took them.
- 벤이 스미스필드 유아원 다니지?
- 다녀, 왜?
-Doesn't Ben go to Smithfield Day School?
-Yeah. Why?
- 스팅 아들도 거기 다닌데
- 알아, 벤이랑 같은 반이야
-Sting has a son that goes there too.
-I know. He's in Ben's class.
그런데 여태 말 안 했단 말이야?
공룡 이야기는 그렇게 해대구?
You knew and never said anything? With
all the stupid dinosaur stuff you tell us?
공룡 이야기 이제 안 할게
근데 화석 이야기는 해도 돼?
Fine, no more dinosaur stuff.
Can I talk about fossils?
스팅 아들 7살, 사진도 있어
"Sting's son, 7 years old."
And there's a picture.
뭐 읽어? "맨해튼 사립학교
유괴범 지침서"?
What are you reading, "The Kidnapper's
Guide to Manhattan Private Schools"?
뉴욕 매거진이야, 시내
최고 학교들을 소개하고 있다구
It's New York Magazine. It's an article
about the city's best schools.
- 그래서 스팅이랑 잘 알아?
- 실은 한 번도 만난 적 없어
-So how well do you know Sting?
-I actually haven't even met him.
어쩌지? 금요일날 스팅 콘서트
가고 싶은데, 매진이야
Yeah. That's too bad. I really wanna go to
his concert Friday, but it's sold out.
직접 만나서 표를 얻으면 어때?
I know! Why don't you
meet him and get tickets.
두 장 얻으면 너 데려갈게
If you get two, I'll take you.
내일 내가 벤 데리러 가니까
어쩌면 볼 수 있을지도 몰라
I'm picking Ben up tomorrow.
Maybe he'll be there.
그렇지
좋겠다, 스팅도 만나보고
There you go. You're so lucky.
You might get to meet Sting tomorrow.
그러라고 애를 낳는 거야
That's why you have kids.
- 안녕
- 어서 와
-Hey, guys.
-Hey.
모니카 안녕, 부츠도 안녕
Hi, Monica. Hi, boots.
봤지?
아주 실용적인 부츠라구
See, Chandler? I'm getting a lot of use out
of them already. They're very practical.
드레스, 치마, 바지
뭐든지 어울려
You can wear them
with dresses, skirts, pants..
숏팬츠 입고
길에서 돈도 벌 수 있겠네
You wear them with shorts on the corner
and earn the money to pay for them.
- 와, 예쁘다
- 발이 너무 아파
-Wow, they're beautiful.
-They hurt so much.
- 뭐?
- 이거 만든 사람이
-What?
-The guy who made these..
발가락을 다 죽이려고
작정했나봐
hates feet
and wants to see them die.
그럼 나 줘
난 발가락 느껴본 지 오래됐어
Give them to me.
I haven't felt my feet in years.
항상 신고 다니기로 챈들러랑
약속해서 그냥 못 줘
I can't. I told Chandler I'd wear them
all the time. I can't just give them away.
- 그럼 환불해
- 그것도 안돼
-Then get your money back and return them.
-I can't do that either.
밑창도 닳고
내 피가 흥건하다구
The soles are scuffed up, and the
insides are filled with my blood.
- 어서 와
- 학교에서 벤 데려오는 길이야
-Hey.
-Hey, I just picked up Ben from school.
벤은 어딨어?
I don't think you did
a very thorough job.
캐롤 집에 내려줬어
I dropped him off at Carol's.
아무튼 표는 못 구할 거 같아
Anyway, it turns out I'm not gonna
get those tickets, though.
왜 안돼?
Oh, no. Why not?
벤과 스팅 아들이 사이가
안 좋대
It turns out Ben and Sting's son
do not get along.
- 왜?
- 스팅 아들이...
-How come?
-Apparently, Sting's son made fun..
벤 엄마가 "레즈비언"이라고
놀렸나 봐
of the fact that Ben's moms
are "lesbenims."
사이가 안 좋으면
친구가 되도록 하면 되지
Wait. If they don't get along, smooth
things over. Make them be friends.
- 억지로 친구를 만들 수는 없잖아
- 할 수 있어
-You can't force kids to be friends.
-Sure you can.
블록을 주고 플레이펜에서
둘이 놀게 해
Give them some blocks.
Put them in a playpen.
- 플레이펜? 벤은 7살이야
- 7살?
-Playpen? Ben's 7.
-Your kid is 7?
정말 작네
He's really small.
- 제발 표 구해 줘
- 미안하지만, 난 못해
-Please get the tickets.
-I'm sorry. I just can't do it.
- 할 수 있어, 스팅도 그렇게 말했어
- 뭐라고?
-Yes, you can. Sting says so himself.
-What?
로스는 할 수 있다
미안하지만...
Look, I'm sorry..
로스는 할 수 있다
Phoebe?
- 피비?
- 로스는 표를 구할 수 있다
로스는 표를 구할 수 있다
미래의 패션 슈퍼스타 납시오
Here she is: future fashion superstar.
- 조이, 내가...
- 우리 막내 디나야
-Oh, Joey, I'm hardly..
-My little sister Dina.
- 디나 안녕, 만나서 반가워요
- 안녕하세요
-Hi, Dina. Nice to meet you.
-Hi.
시간 내줘서 정말 고마워요
조이한테 이야기 많이 들었어요
Thanks so much for meeting with me.
Joey's told me so much about you.
디나가 너무 좋아해
This is so exciting for her.
- 랄프 로렌이 방금 미소도 지었어
- 제대로 본 거 맞아?
-Ralph Lauren smiled at her in the elevator.
-You sure it was at you?
엘리베이터 불이 켜지는 걸
좋아하거든
Because he likes it sometimes
when the buttons light up.
그럼 두 "패션... 주의자"들께서
이야기를 나눠
Well, I'll let you two "fashists"
get down to business.
많이 배워, 그리고 혹시
옷 얻으면 나도 셔츠 하나만...
You, be good, learn a lot. And if she takes
you to the freebie room, I need shirts..
남자가 개 등에 타고 있는 그림
있는 거 말고...
but none with that creepy logo with
the guy riding the dog, holding the bone.
알았어
Okay. All right, Dina.
그럼, 먼저 패션 분야에서
어떻게 일을 시작할 수 있는지
Well, let's talk about the different
areas of fashion..
이야기 할 게요
that you could get involved in.
디자인을 하려면 학위가
있어야 해요
Let's see, there's design. But you may
need a whole other degree for that.
- 판매직도 좋죠, 여행도 할 수 있고...
- 저 패션에 관심 없어요
-Sales is great. You get to travel.
-I don't care about fashion.
임신했는데, 당신도 그렇다면서요?
그러니 좀 도와줘요
I'm pregnant. And I know you are too,
so you gotta help me.
그리고 마케팅 분야도 있어요
Then there's marketing.
- 왜 그래?
- 아냐, 하품하는 거야
-What's wrong?
-Nothing. I just was yawning.
- 오늘 회사 파티 있는 거 잊지마
- 그게 오늘밤이야?
-Don't forget, my office party's tonight.
-That's tonight?
비밀 산타 선물 다 잊어 버렸네
I forgot all about the "secret Santa" gift.
우리가 이거 좋아하던가?
Do we like this?
거기 꼭 가야 하는 건 아니지?
We don't really have to go to this thing,
do we?
회사 파티 싫어하는 건 알아
그래도 새 부츠 신을 수 있잖아
I know that you don't like my office parties,
but you can wear your new boots.
모든 일에는 항상 좋은 면이
있는 거라구
See? Every cloud has
a supple leather lining.
- 오늘은 부츠 안 신을래
- 왜?
-I don't wanna wear the boots tonight.
-Why not?
상사들이 보고 당신 월급이
너무 후하다고 생각할 지도 몰라
I'm worried your bosses will see them
and think they pay you too much money.
아니면 부하 직원들이
월급 올려 달라고 할 수도 있고
Or your assistant will see them
and want a raise.
혹시 내가 부츠 가격 매기는 회사
다니는 줄 알고 있어?
Do you think I work some kind of
boot-pricing company?
오늘밤에 입을 옷은
부츠랑 안 어울려
I picked out this outfit I wanna wear,
and the boots don't go with it.
치마, 드레스, 바지 어디나
어울린다며
You said those boots go with skirts,
dresses and pants.
뭐 입으려고 그래?
마술사 복장?
What are you planning on wearing,
a chicken suit?
좋아, 그렇게 원하면
부츠 신을게
Fine. If you want me to,
I'll wear the boots.
지금 방에 가서 옷 입어 볼 거야
In fact, I'll go into my room right now
and try the outfit on.
부츠와 함께 크리스마스 파티를!
Christmas party in my boots!
나 못하겠어요
I can't go in there. I can't tell him.
괜찮을 거예요
나한테도 얼마나 잘해줬는데요
It's gonna be okay.
He has been incredibly supportive of me.
혹시라도 조이가 화내면
얼른 미트볼 샌드위치를 주면 되죠
And if he gets a little upset,
that's what the meatball sub is for.
- 고마워요
- 가요
-Thank you.
-Okay.
헤이! 패션 아가씨들
Hey! It's my fashion girls.
- 무슨 일 있어?
- 먼저 자리에 앉아
-What's wrong?
-Why don't you sit down.
디나가 할 말이 있대
Dina has something
that she wants to tell you.
무슨 일인데?
엄마 문제야? 엄마가 아파?
What's going on?
Is it Mom? Is she sick?
아빠 심장 문제야?
Is it Dad's heart?
그거 샌드위치야?
Is that a sandwich?
- 엄마 아빠는 모두 괜찮아
- 그거 샌드위치구나?!
-Mom and Dad are fine.
-Is that a sandwich?!
조이, 네가 알아야 할 게 있어
디나?
Joey, there's something
that you should know. Dina?
- 나 임신했어
- 뭐?
-I'm pregnant.
-What?
지금, 얼른 샌드위치 줘!
Now. Give him the sandwich!
뭔가 잘못 됐을 거야
임신했을 리가 없어
Obviously, this is a mistake.
You can't be pregnant.
왜냐하면 임신하려면
섹스를 해야 하니까
Because you have to have sex
to get pregnant.
나도 오빠처럼 25살까지
기다리려고 했어
Joe, I tried to wait until
I was 25, like you did.
뭐라구? 디나...
What? Dina..
그럴 리 없어, 넌 착한 애야
대학교도 나왔잖아
I can't believe this. You're the good one.
You went to college! Both years!
도대체 어떤 놈이야?
Who did this to you?
바비 코르소, 정말 좋은 남자야
나도 좋아하고, 되게 웃겨
Bobby Corso. But he's a real nice guy.
I like him a lot. He's real funny.
"웃겨서" 임신했다구?
디나, 웃기면 웃어야지!
You got pregnant for "funny"?
Dina, if he's funny, laugh!
- 금방 올테니 여기서 기다려!
- 왜? 어디 가는데?
-I'll be back. Stay here!
-Why? Where you going?
지금은 널 못 보겠어
I can't look at you right now.
그러게
I know.
여기 있구나, 벤
Oh, there you are, Ben.
벤 맞지?
You're Ben, right?
피비 아줌마, 여기서 뭐 하세요?
Aunt Phoebe, what are you doing here?
어떤 친구랑 사이가 안 좋다며?
I heard you're having a problem
with one of the boys.
그래서 내가 도와주려고
온 거야
So I thought I'd come and sit you both down,
have a little talk and make it all okay.
이름이 스팅 아들이라던데
Now, the boy's name is Sting's son.
잭? 바보 같아서 그 애 싫어요
Jack? I hate him. He's a jerk.
겉보기에는 바보 같지만
Sometimes people may seem
like jerks on the outside..
아버지가 유명하잖니
but they have famous fathers.
갈게요, 저쪽에서 더그가
기다리고 있어요
I have to go. My friend Doug
is waiting for me over there.
와, 저 애 빌리 조엘 닮았다
Wow, your friend Doug
looks a lot like Billy Joel.
- 아빠가 빌리 조앨 맞니?
- 아뇨, 치과의사예요
-Is that who his father is?
-No. His dad's a dentist.
쟤랑은 친구면서...
Him, you're friends with.
- 뭘 도와 드릴까요?
- 네, 잭 부모님을 찾고 있어요
-Excuse me, can I help you with something?
-Yes. I'm looking for Jack's parents.
- 학부모 되세요?
- 벤이랑 같이 왔어요
-Are you with one of the students?
-I'm with Ben.
- 벤 엄마 중 한 분이세요?
- 네, 맞아요
-Are you one of Ben's mothers?
-I am one of Ben's mothers.
제가 레즈비언이에요
I'm a lesbian.
부모님께 말씀드리기가
참 어려웠죠
It was difficult coming out
to my parents.
안녕하세요
제니 분이에요
Well, hi. I'm Jenny Boon.
I'm a new teacher here.
- 캐롤은 만난 적이 있어요
- 그럼 제가 수잔이겠군요
-I've only met your partner, Carol.
-That would make me Susan.
벤 문제로 잭 부모님을
만나시려구요?
Right. Are you looking for Jack's parents
to discuss his problems with Ben?
제 생각엔 부모들이 만나서
이야기를 해야 할 것 같아요
I think the parents should sit down together
and have a conversation.
그게 좋겠어요!
Yeah, let's do that!
정말 좋은 생각이에요
That sounds good.
저하고 캐롤 그리고 스팅이
만나서 이야기를 해야겠어요
We should sit down and talk.
Me, my lover, Carol, and the Stings.
- 그런데 어떻게 연락하죠?
- 연락 명단에 전화 번호가 있어요
-How will I get in touch with them?
-Their number's on the contact sheet.
저도 1장 주시겠어요?
캐롤이 버렸어요
Could I get a copy of that?
Carol threw it out. She lost ours.
엄청 산만한 사람이거든요
그래도 엉덩이는 끝내주죠
She's such a scatterbrain.
But, man, what a hot piece of ass.
- 파티 나쁘지 않았지?
- 응, 춤추는 게 있는 줄 몰랐어
-You know, that party wasn't bad.
-Yeah. I didn't know there'd be dancing.
재밌게 하려구 몰래 넣은 거지
That was a fun surprise.
- 택시가 없네, 걸어가야겠다
- 안돼, 못 걸어
-I don't see a cab. Maybe we should walk.
-No, we can't walk.
저기 택시 있다, 이봐요
No. Hey, there's a cab.
그거 경찰차야
That's a police car.
나쁜 짓 해서
우리 실어가라고 할까?
Maybe we could commit a crime,
have them pick us up.
- 지하철역까지 별로 멀지 않아
- 알았어
-It's 15 blocks to the subway. Come on.
-Okay.
저 맨홀로 가면 지하철역까지
갈 수 있을까?
Do you think we can get to the subway
if we climb through that manhole?
- 도대체 왜 그래?
- 못 걷겠어, 이제 됐어?
-What's going on?
-I can't walk, okay?
- 부츠 정말 잘못 샀어
- 뭐라구?
-These boots were a huge mistake.
-What?
자기 말대로 사지 말았어야 했어
발가락 아파 죽겠어
You were right. I never should have bought
them. They're killing me, one toe at a time.
- 너무 꽉 끼는 구나, 그렇지?
- 자기 말이 맞다고 했잖아
-So they're really tight, huh?
-I just said you were right, sweetie.
아파 죽을 지경인 거 안보여?
Isn't it clear I'm delirious from the pain?
내 말이 맞았군, 이게 바로
옳았을 때의 기분이야
So I was right. This is what
it feels like to be right.
굉장히 불안정하군
It's oddly unsettling.
집에 어떻게 갈거야?
등에 업혀?
How are we gonna we get home?
Maybe a piggyback ride?
나를 업는다고 상황이
나아질 것 같지 않은데
I don't think me getting on your back
is gonna improve matters.
옳은 게 좋은 것만도 아니군
Wow, being right sure doesn't help
with the funny.
- 업혀
- 알았어, 기다려
-Hop on.
-Okay, wait.
먼저 부츠 좀 벗고
Let me just get my boots off first.
오, 세상에
Oh, God.
자기 아픈 건 알겠는데
난 좀 흥분되는 걸
I know you're in pain right now,
but I'm a little turned-on.
혹시 걷고 있는데 아이가 아래로
빠질까 봐 걱정한 적 있어요?
Do you ever worry that you'll be walking
and your baby will just slip out?
무슨 대학교 나왔어요?
What college was that, Dina?
어머나, 바비?
Oh, my God. Bobby?
안녕, 디나
Hi, Dina. Good to see you.
- 조이, 지금 뭐 하는 거야?
- 해야 할 일을 하는 거지
-Joey, what are you doing?
-Just what needs to be done.
- 이 자리에 하객들을 모시고...
- 미친 짓이야, 이건
-Dearly beloved, we're gathered here..
-This is crazy.
하느님과 이야기할 때는
방해하지 말아줄래?
Don't interrupt me
when I'm talking to God!
- 어디까지 했지? 이 사람을 신랑...?
- 싫어!
-Where were we? Do you take this man..?
-No!
- 신랑으로 맞아야 해
- 싫어, 안 할거야!
-You'll take him.
-No, I won't!
- 넌 발언할 수 없어
- 할거야
-You don't get a say.
-Yes, I do.
- 방금 "할거야"라고 했지?
- 조이, 이제 그만해!
-I heard "l do." We're halfway there. You.
-All right, Joey, that is enough!
아름답고 감동적이긴 하지만
이건 불법이야
As beautiful and moving
as this ceremony is, this is not legal.
증인도 없고 신랑은
신발 한 짝밖에 없잖아
They don't have a marriage license or
witnesses, and the groom only has one shoe.
다른 한 짝으로
저를 때렸거든요
Yeah, he took the other one off
and hit me with it.
그럼 내가 어쩌겠어?
What am I supposed to do?
저들도 성인이니
스스로 결정하도록 해줘야지
You're supposed to realize they are adults
and that can make their own decisions.
그렇게는 못해
임신할 정도로 뭘 모른다구!
No, they can't. They were
stupid enough to get knocked up!
피임이 항상 성공하는 건
아니야, 그렇지?
Contraceptives are not
always effective. Right?
- 네, 저희는 피임 안 했어요
- 이봐, 협조 좀 해요!
-Yeah. We kind of didn't use any.
-Come on, kids, a little help here!
와우! 정말 근사하다!
Wow! This place is incredible!
스팅의 펜이네
Sting's pen..
피비한테 준 펜...
that he gave to Phoebe.
와우, 비밀 통로다
Come on, secret passageway.
- 어서 오세요
- 안녕하세요
-Hi.
트루디예요, 벤 엄마 되시죠?
I'm Trudie. You must be Ben's mum.
- 아님 제가 여기 왜 왔겠어요?
- 앉으세요
-Why else would I be here?
-Why don't you sit down.
잭과 벤이 사이가 별로
안 좋다고 들었어요
I gather Jack and Ben
haven't been getting along lately.
양쪽 이야기를 들어야 알겠지만
I'm sure there are two sides to this story.
제가 듣기로는
벤이 좀 바보 같다더군요
But all I've heard is that
Ben's a bit of a "poo-poo-head."
- 잭 아빠는 안 오시나요?
- 안 와요
-I'm sorry, won't Jack's father be joining us?
-No.
제 생각엔 부모들이 모두
모이는 것이
I see. You see, I think it would be better
for the children..
아이들한테 좋을 듯 싶어요
벤의 생모 생부만 빼구요
if all the parents were here. Except for,
you know, Ben's birth mother and father.
죄송한데, 잭 아빠가 바빠서요
Well, I'm sorry.
Jack's father's not available.
금요일 밤 8시쯤으로
다시 약속을 잡을까요?
Okay. Well, then, could we reschedule
for Friday night, perhaps at 8:00?
콘서트 때문에 안될 거예요
No, I know that wouldn't work.
My husband's in concert.
그렇군요
시간이 빠듯하겠네요
Concert. Yeah.
That does put us in quite a pickle.
제가 콘서트 전후로 바쁘거든요
남편 분은 콘서트 중에 바쁠거고
I'm busy before and after the concert,
and he's obviously busy during.
그러니까 지금 아이들 이야기를
하는 것이 좋겠어요
So I guess you and I should talk
about Jack and Ben right now.
아니면...
Unless.. Unless..
제가 콘서트장에 가는 건
어때요?
Okay, I would be willing
to go to the concert..
가는 동안 내내 아이들
생각을 하면서...
all the while thinking
about the children.
- 지금 표 때문에 오신 거예요?
- 정말 고마워요, 4장만 주세요
-Are you here for tickets?
-Thank you. Four would be great.
이런 식으로 아들을 이용하는
사람한테는 표 줄 수 없어요
I'm not giving concert tickets to someone
who'd use their son like this.
잘됐네요
벤은 제 아들이 아니에요
Then you're in luck. Ben's not my son.
방금 비상벨 눌렀어요
Look, I've just pressed a button
triggering a silent alarm.
- 곧 경찰이 도착할 거예요
- 폴리스요? 여기 에요?
-Any minute now, the police will be here.
-The Police? Here?
재회예요?
A reunion?
이제 5블록만 더 가면 돼
Okay, 10 blocks down. Five to go.
- 잠깐! 멈춰 봐!
- 미안, 쉬었다 갈까?
-Oh, wait! Stop, stop!
-Oh, I'm sorry. Do you need a break?
내 부츠! 가격표 보게 조금만
가까이 가줄래?
My boots in tan! Can you get a little closer
so I see the price?
여기서도 보여
남편 하나 값이야
I can see it from right here.
It'll cost you one husband.
미안해, 이제 걸을 수 있어
내 부츠 줘
I'm sorry. I can walk the rest
of the way now. Just give me my boots.
- 나한테 없는데
- 나도 없어, 어디 있지?
-I don't have your boots.
-I don't have them either. Where are they?
내가 풀 뜯어먹고 쉬는 동안
자루 뒤져 봐
Why don't you check in one of my
saddlebags while I chew on a bale of hay?
다시 돌아가서 가져와야겠어!
Okay. My God, we gotta go back
and get them!
그 부츠 다시 신을 거야?
Are you ever gonna wear the boots again?
당연하지
아주 실용적인 부츠라니까
Yes, I am. Okay? They're very practical.
- 바지에도 신고 치마하고도...
- 자기야, 자기야
-I could wear them with pants or skirts..
-Honey. Honey.
알았어, 다시 안 신을 거야
그래도 작별인사를 못했잖아
Okay, I'll never wear them again. I just
didn't get a chance to say goodbye.
그럼 저 부츠한테 인사해
You know what? You can say goodbye
to the tan ones.
- 알았어
- 그래
-Okay. All right.
-Okay.
부츠 안녕, 잠깐 기다려!
Bye, boots. Wait! Half off!
결혼 안 한다고 해서
큰일 나는 거 아니야
Just because they're not getting
married doesn't mean it's a disaster.
- 나름대로 계획이 있을 수도 있고
- 좋아, 계획이 뭔지 들어보자
-Maybe they have a plan.
-Oh, okay, let's hear their plan.
앞으로 둘의 계획이 뭐야?
Now, what's the future look like
for Dina and Bobby?
글쎄요...
Well..
제 밴드가 잘 됐으면 좋겠어요
I really have high hopes for my band.
- 정말 재미있는 사람이네
- 그러지 마
-You were right. He is funny.
-Now, wait a minute.
네가 배우가 되겠다고 했을 때도
사람들이 비웃었어
I bet when you told people you wanted
to be an actor, they laughed at you.
바비, 당신 밴드에 대해서
이야기 좀 해줘요
Come on, Bobby,
tell us a little bit about your band.
저하고 루스터라는 친구가 하는데
밴드 명은 얼간이들이에요
Well, it's just me and my pal Rooster.
The band's name is Numbnuts.
정말?
Really?
아이를 가졌으면
결혼을 해야 해
If you're having a baby,
you should be married.
그게 바비라도 말이야
이봐, 칭찬이 아니거든?
Even if it is to Bobby.
Dude, that's not a compliment.
- 오빠가 내 말 안들을 줄 알았어
- 이제 어떻게 할거야?
-I knew you wouldn't be supportive.
-So, what are you gonna do?
아기 낳아서 혼자 기른다구?
남편도 없이?
Have the baby and raise it by yourself?
Without a husband?
미혼모가 되게 할 수는 없어!
그건 인생을 망치는 짓이야!
You can't be a single mother alone!
You're gonna ruin your life!
- 그럼 내 인생도 망친 거야?
- 너하고는 달라
-Excuse me. Am I ruining my life?
-No, it's different for you.
넌 강하잖아
저렇게 어리석지도 않고
You're so strong. You're not some dumb kid
who doesn't know what she's doing.
- 뭐라구?
- 한 번에 임산부 한 명씩!
-Excuse me?
-One pregnant woman at a time, please!
난 네가 잘 되길 바라는 거야
I just want you to be okay.
바비랑 억지로 결혼시키면
잘 될 거 같아?
So forcing her to marry Bobby
is gonna make that happen?
그럴 수도 있지
Maybe.
그래, 얼간이들은
무슨 음악을...?
Yeah. So, what kind of music
does Numbnuts..?
아냐, 됐어! 난 못해!
Oh, forget it! I can't!
나 정말 두렵지만 도와준다면
할 수 있을 것 같아
I am scared to death about this. But I
think I can do it. I just need some help.
- 그리고 바비도 항상 있을거구
- 그럼
-Bobby's gonna be here the whole time.
-You bet I am.
그리고 아까 질문에 답하자면
우린 갱스터랩 해요
And to answer your earlier question,
we're straight-up gangster rap.
오빠가 레이첼을 많이 도와줬다는
말 들었어
Look, Rachel's told me how much easier
you've made all this on her.
- 왜 나한테는 그렇게 못해?
- 넌 내 막내동생이니까!
-Why can't you do that for me?
-Because you're my baby sister!
오빠는 내가 세상에서
제일 좋아하는 남자야
And you're my big brother. You're
my favorite guy in the whole world.
부모님보다도 오빠한테
말하는 게 더 겁났어
I'm not even scared to tell Mom and Dad.
I was scared of telling you.
난 부모님이 더 무서운데
어쨌거나
I'd be scared of them, but all right.
오빠를 화나게 하고
아기를 갖고 싶진 않아
I can't stand the thought of having
this baby with you mad at me.
아이에게 삼촌이 있으면 좋겠어
I want him to have his uncle.
조이 삼촌이 되어 줄 거야?
Is my baby gonna have his Uncle Joey?
당연히 내가 조이 삼촌이
될 거지
Of course he's gonna have
his Uncle Joey.
우린 잘 할거야, 결혼 안 하더라도
아이를 정말 잘 키울거야
We'll be all right. Even if we're not
married, this baby will be so loved.
- 우리뿐만이 아니지
- 그렇지
-And not just by us.
-That's right.
삼촌도 있고
By his uncle too.
당신도 있고
And by you.
바비, 둘이 좀 시간을 가지라고
자리를 피해주면 어때요?
Bobby, why don't we come over here and
let them have a little moment, okay?
이리 와
Come here.
정말 이상한 사람이네?
No, seriously, what's wrong with you?
뭐게?
Guess what.
우리 서로 아는 사이지
We're good. We're good.
We know each other.
그래서...
So..
- 아무튼 맞춰봐
- 어, 또 있어?
-anyway, guess what.
-Oh, there's more?
내가 정말 사랑스러울 걸
스팅 표를 얻었거든!
You're gonna love me so much.
I got Sting tickets!
정말이야, 사랑해!
어떻게 구했어?
Oh, my God, I do love you!
How did you do it?
글쎄
Well, let's just say:
로스는 할 수 있다고 할까
- 자리가 어디야?
- 가운데 발코니
-Where are the seats?
-Middle balcony.
스팅 가족들로부터
Would you say that's
more than 50 yards away..
45미터 이상 떨어진 자리야?
from Sting, his wife
or a member of his family?
- 응
- 그럼 위법이 아니지, 나도 가!
-Yeah.
-Then that's not breaking the law. I'm there!